thinkexist.com 2007-10-09

# Finding quotations was never this easy

    **PRIVACY AND SECURITY POLICY**

At ThinkExist, we value your privacy. We operate under a strict set of privacy principles:   

The only information ThinkExist obtains about individual visitors to its Web site is information supplied voluntarily by visitors. For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the user’s domain name.   

In cases when ThinkExist may need personal information to provide visitors with services tailored especially for them, or to inform them about new features or services, visitors are asked explicitly for that information.   

All identifiable information provided by members (name, email…) will not be disclosed to anyone unless members specifically request ThinkExist to do so.   

Only statistical information of our members as a group (usage habits, demographics) may be shared with any partner of ThinkExist; no identifiable information will be shared at any time. ThinkExist employs appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of personal information.

Delete/Deactivate Policy

Users may unsubscribe to any of our electronic newsletters at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every newsletter.   

Newsletter Privacy Policy   

ThinkExist maintains a strict "NO-SPAM" policy. Your information, including your e-mail address will not be given to any third party if you sign up for one of our newsletters.  

Polling   

ThinkExist.com offers interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what the ThinkExist audience thinks about important issues. ThinkExist uses a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with information about individual users. 

Surveys  

Occasionally, ThinkExist conducts user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our advertisers and partners. We never share any information about specific individuals with any third party. 

Tracking .Gif’s  

ThinkExist and its advertisers may use tracking or single-pixel gif images to count Web page accesses and gather some general statistical information. ThinkExist does not gather personal information through the use of these images. Some advertisers may use tracking gifs that can track personal information from cookies that may have been previously placed on a user's computer.   

Consent 

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of information by ThinkExist as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

How to Reach Us  

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy please contact us. We will make every reasonable effort to find and correct the problem promptly.
